// Counter Data JS

// An array of objects listing a random difficult trigonometry problem and the answer with ids
const counter = [
	{
		id: 1,
		problem: 'sin(2x) = 1/2',
		answer: 'x = 30 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		problem: 'cos(2x) = 1/2',
		answer: 'x = 60 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		problem: 'tan(2x) = 1/2',
		answer: 'x = 15 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		problem: 'sin(2x) = 1/3',
		answer: 'x = 60 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		problem: 'cos(2x) = 1/3',
		answer: 'x = 30 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		problem: 'tan(2x) = 1/3',
		answer: 'x = 45 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		problem: 'sin(2x) = 1/4',
		answer: 'x = 45 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 8,
		problem: 'cos(2x) = 1/4',
		answer: 'x = 45 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		problem: 'tan(2x) = 1/4',
		answer: 'x = 22.5 degrees',
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		problem: 'sin(2x) = 1/5',
		answer: 'x = 36 degrees',
	},
];

export default counter;
